This is a work of fiction.
Underage drinking is strongly prohibited and illegal.
Scenes involving alcohol with forceful consumption
and shameful acts are not encouraged.
Please view this as a comedy.
Furthermore, all characters appearing
in this work are of legal age.
Grand Blue Dreaming
This work is an original copyrighted material
of the Content Provider. Unauthorized reproduction
or distribution of this work in any form or manner
is prohibited. Some viewers might find this work disturbing
as it may contain strong language, a degree of violence
or adult situations. Viewer discretion is advised.
Please watch it at your own risk.
The story, names, characters and incidents portrayed
in this work are fictitious. No identification with actual
persons, organizations, religions, places and products
is intended. The Content Provider, the producers
and related parties shall have no liability,
as to the accuracy, legality, safety or suitability
for any purpose of the information provided in this work.
The views and opinions expressed herein do not reflect
the views and opinions of the Content Provider,
or any of its affiliates, partners, subsidiaries, or Licensee.
MIYAKO AIRPORT
（梓(あずさ)）う～ん 到着っと
We've arrived!
-So this is Miyakojima.
-It's pretty far away.
（愛菜(あいな)）ここが宮古島(みやこじま)
（千紗(ちさ)）結構 遠かったね
（シャッター音）
Riding a plane within the same prefecture is weird.
（奈々華(ななか)）県内で飛行機に
乗るなんて 新鮮よね
This island is closer to Taiwan than Japan.
（伊織(いおり)）本島より
台湾のほうが近いらしいな
No wonder it was so far!
（耕平(こうへい)）そりゃ 遠いわけだ
-Sorry.
-We didn't notice we were doing it.
（伊織）すみません
（耕平）つい 無意識で
We're going to dive now. You can't drink.
今から潜るのに お酒はダメよ
You guys fit right in now.
２人とも すっかり
ＰａＢ(パブ)に染まったねえ
（クラクション）
（一同）ん？
Hey, you guys!
（東(あずま)）おーい お前ら
（横手(よこて)）無事 着いたみたいだな
It looks like you arrived safely.
-Thanks for coming.
-No problem.
わざわざ 来てもらって
すみません
いいってことよ
We got here last night.
俺たちは 昨日の晩に
着いてたからな
-You got here pretty early.
-We're going diving in the morning.
（伊織）ずいぶん 早いですね
（東）朝から潜るんだ
We wanted to get here a day early.
（横手）前日入りしとかないと
We're looking forward to Otori afterwards even more.
（東）まあ そのあとの
オトーリのほうが楽しみだが
-Otori?
（耕平･伊織）オトーリ？
-It's a drinking custom from Miyakojima.
-Haven't you heard about it?
宮古式の飲み方だそうだ
（横手）聞いてないのか？
今回の合宿の目的の８割は―
Otori is one of the main reasons
we came on this trip.
オトーリなんだぞ
（耕平･伊織）あっ！
WHAT IS OTORI!
-So that's what it was!
あれか！
By the way, I saw some rumors on the Internet
そういえば ネットで
うわさを見かけたんだが
that some restaurants put out signs saying
"No Miyakojima people."
“宮古人(みやこんちゅ)お断り”なんて
看板を出してる店があるとか
Is it because Otori is too wild?
（伊織）オトーリってやつが
すごすぎてですか？
That's just an urban legend.
さすがに それは都市伝説だろ
No one would drink and act that badly.
（横手）そんな ひでえ飲み方
するやつがいるもんか
You're right....
（伊織･耕平）ですよね
NO PaB MEMBERS
-What did you guys do last night?
あんたら ゆうべ
何やったんですか!?
-Well, enough of that.
-It's finally time to make your debut as divers.
まあ それはそれとしてだ
いよいよ ダイバーデビューだな
（伊織）ああ…
それなんですけど 実は…
About that. Actually...
He had a fever yesterday and stayed in bed.
こいつ 昨日
熱出して 寝込みまして
-Really?
-So you didn't get your license?
マジか
じゃあ ライセンス
取れなかったのか
This is embarrassing...
（伊織）お恥ずかしい…
-I was looking forward to it a little too much.
-What do you mean?
ちょっと
楽しみにしすぎちゃいまして
（東）なんだ そりゃ
（横手）遠足で 熱出す子どもか
Getting sick on a trip? Like a little kid?
That's why I can't go diving with you.
なので 俺は
一緒に潜れないんですよ
-I see.
-That's too bad.
（東）そうか
（横手）そりゃ 残念だな
おお～！　すげえスピード！
Wow, it's so fast!
The wind feels really good!
風がすっごく気持ちいいよね！
ん？　なんだ？
（愛菜）んっ…
What did you say?
か… 顔 近いから！
You're too close!
フッ… 初心者が
はしゃぎやがって
-The amateur is getting excited.
-What?
ああん？
てめえのは聞こえてっぞ！
I heard you!
You've only done it twice yourself!
てめえだって
まだ２回目だろうが！
Want me to teach the amateur
how to behave on the boat?
なんなら 初心者君に
船上のマナーでも教えてやろうか
Stop it! There are other people here too!
やめなさい！　ほかにも
お客さん いるんだから
All right, everyone.
それでは 皆さん
ミーティング始めますよ
Let's begin our meeting!
Okay!
（一同）うお～っす
That's what it's going to be like.
という感じのポイントです
We're planning to dive to a depth of 17 meters
for 40 minutes.
深度は17メートル
潜水時間は
40分を予定しています
All right, everyone. Please get ready!
それじゃ 皆さん
準備をお願いします
Okay!
（一同）うお～っす
Okay, okay! Let's go change in the dressing room!
はいはい！
更衣室で着替えましょうね！
-What are you going to do?
-About what?
お前はどうするんだ？
（伊織）何がだ？
You have to have a license to dive 17 meters.
深度17メートルだと
ライセンスがないと…
I'll be okay.
それなら 大丈夫だ
They're letting me join their trial dives
for the first and second dives.
１～２本目は 体験ダイビングに
まぜてもらうことになった
What about the third dive?
３本目はどうするんだ？
Everyone's planning to go on three dives.
みんな ３本潜る予定
みたいだけど
I'll just wait on the boat.
俺は 船の上で待機だな
Maybe I should ask them to let me join them too.
私も そっちに
まぜてもらおうかな…
（伊織）は？　なんでだ？
-Why?
-I'm not confident I'll be able to dive well.
だって うまく潜れるか
自信ないし…
What are you talking about?
何をバカなことを
The guys will help you, and you have her too.
先輩たちも
フォローしてくれるし―
こいつだって いるだろ？
The ocean is so beautiful here.
こんな きれいな海なんだから
行けるところまで行ってこいよ
You should go as far as you can.
うん…
Okay.
Everyone who's here for the trial dive,
gather here please!
（インストラクター）
体験ダイビングの方―
集まってください
おっと じゃあ
そっちはそっちで楽しんでこいよ
Bye. Have fun!
Go slow and stay calm.
Let's equalize pressure.
（奈々華）ゆっくりと
落ち着いて 耳抜きしながらね
Okay!
（愛菜･耕平）分かりました
（一同）んん～！
The sea turtles came really close.
ウミガメが
近くまで来てくれたな
That was amazing!
すごかったですよね！
We were lucky to see a parent with a child.
親子連れとは ついてたねえ
It's as amazing as 2D!
２次元のような
すばらしさだった…
Were you able to see it, Iori?
伊織のとこからは
見えなかったか？
-No. Too bad.
-We took pictures. Here.
残念ながら
写真なら撮ったぞ
ほれ こんな感じだ
（伊織）おっ
It looked like this.
（伊織）おお！　できれば
近くで見たかったですね
I wish I could've seen that up close.
If you get your license,
you'll have another chance.
なあに ライセンスを取れば
またチャンスはあるさ
Work harder next time, junior.
次は頑張れよ 後輩
Hearing you, of all people, say that really pisses me off.
お前に言われると
異様に腹が立つな
（話し声）
I'll get the tea.
お茶 取ってきます
ハァ…
（千紗）あっ
（千紗）ああ…
ここ 水族館に似て…
This looks just like the aquarium.
I want to see it up close next time.
次は もっと近くで
見てみたいかな
（千紗）あ…
He can't see it from over there...
（千紗）
あそこからじゃ 遠いよね
（耳が鳴る音）
That was so magical.
すごい幻想的でした
It makes me wish I had a camera!
あれは カメラが欲しくなりますね
The light is just right at this time of day.
光のさし方が
いい時間帯だったからな
You don't get to see that every day.
なかなか見られるもんじゃないぞ
Where's Iori?
あれ？　伊織は？
He said he was going to rest on the deck.
デッキで休むとか言ってたな
I see.
ふうん そっか…
Iori has been pretty quiet today.
今日の伊織は
ずいぶん おとなしいねえ
You're right.
確かに
Maybe he's feeling sick.
具合でも悪いのかもしれんな
-Nanaka.
-What's wrong, Chisa-chan?
お姉ちゃん
どうかした？　千紗ちゃん
I'm going to skip the third dive.
私 ３本目はやめとく
My ears ache.
ちょっと 耳 やっちゃって…
You know, Iori...
It's too bad you couldn't dive with everyone today,
but this isn't the last time.
みんなと潜れないのは
残念だけど―
これが最後ってわけじゃないから
We're going somewhere shallow tomorrow
where you can do more trial dives.
明日は 体験でも行ける
浅めのポイントにも行くらしいし
That's right!
そ… そうそう
この前のバイトで―
I got tickets to the aquarium
at work the other day.
水族館の入場券もらったから
よかったら…
If you want...
Chisa.
（伊織）千紗
（千紗）えっ…
The boat really rocks back and forth...
（伊織）船って結構 揺れるのな
（千紗）は？
（伊織）ううっ…
I should have taken the motion sickness pills
like they told me to.
忠告どおり 酔い止め
飲んでおけばよかった
Waiting on the surface before diving...
あと 潜る前の水面待機
-That's pretty rough too.
-Iori.
あれも かなり揺れてキツいな
（千紗）伊織…
（伊織）なんだ？
-What?
-Are you just seasick?
もしかして 酔ってただけ？
What do you mean "just"? I feel horrible.
（伊織）だけとはなんだ
結構 つらいんだぞ
-Come on.
-Sorry.
（千紗）まったく…
（伊織）悪いな
Well, you know, Chisa...
しかしまあ あれだな 千紗
（千紗）ん？
ハァ…
You're a good woman.
お前 いい女だな
What? What are you talking about?
はあ？　何言ってんの？
（伊織）フッ…
You were thinking about me when I was left here alone.
１人で残される俺に
気ぃ使ってくれてたんだろ？
ん… 別に そういうわけじゃ
Well, not really.
Don't worry, Chisa.
大丈夫だって 千紗
I'm not going to hate diving
just because of this.
俺は この程度でダイビングが
嫌いになったりしないからさ
I see.
（千紗）そう
Diving is amazing.
すごいよな ダイビング
-I never imagined it'd be fun on the boat as well.
-The boat?
海の中だけじゃなくて
船まで楽しいとは思わなかった
（千紗）船が？
When we were coming here just now,
I thought to myself...
さっき このポイントに
移動してくるときに思ったんだよ
Talking about what you saw underwater...
海の中で見たものについて
話したり
Eating lunch together on the boat...
ボートの上で
みんなで昼飯 食ったり
Feeling the breeze and the sunlight
while the boat moves...
潮風と日光を浴びながら
移動したり…
It feels amazing.
これって 最高に気持ちいいよな
うん…
The guys are usually loud, but they're so relaxed.
（伊織）いつも騒々しい
先輩たちですら あれだもんな
They're like sunbathing cats.
（千紗）
日光浴中の猫みたいだよね
It's too bad I could only participate in the trial dive.
体験ダイビングになったのは
残念だけど―
-But I want to come again.
-I see.
また来たいと思ったよ
（千紗）そっか
You didn't go on the third dive either,
so you would want to come again too, right?
お前も ３本目
潜れなかったんだから―
リベンジに来たいだろう？
Well, yeah.
まあ そうだけど…
If you treat me.
伊織のおごりなら
You know I don't have much. How can you say that?
俺の懐事情 知ってて
よく言えるな
I'll take you if I win the lottery.
まっ 宝くじでも当たったら
連れてきてやるよ
（千紗）
ん… 期待しないで待ってる
I'm not going to get my hopes up.
All right, everyone! We're done diving now!
では皆さん 以上で
ボートダイビングは終了です
Let's head back to land!
陸に帰りましょう！
（一同）うお～っす！
Okay!
Hey, everyone. Listen.
（時田）みんな 聞いてくれ
It's about Otori.
One of the main reasons we came to Miyakojima.
宮古島に来た理由の８割を占める
オトーリ体験だが…
The restaurant we were planning to go to is closed,
so we had to cancel those plans.
予定していた店が
なぜか臨時休業になったため―
断念することになった
（部員たちの悲鳴）
-Otori means endless drinking, right?
-Yeah.
オトーリって
エンドレス飲みのことだよね？
ああ
We escaped an endless World Championship.
終わりのない世界線から
逃れられたか
It's going to be a peaceful night on Miyakojima tonight--
いやあ これで
平和な宮古島の夜が…
But, we don't come to Miyakojima every day.
（時田）だが せっかく
宮古島まで来たんだ
So let's do our own Otori!
せめて 俺たちなりのオトーリを
やってみようじゃないか！
（部員たち）うおおお！
（耕平･伊織）グッ…
Hey, don't go so crazy, freshman.
（時田）おいおい
そう はしゃぐなよ １年坊
Well, then. Let's begin.
さあ 始めようか…
What do you mean, "our own Otori"?
俺たちなりのオトーリって
なんですか!?
-Don't get so agitated.
-We're about to explain.
まあ そう焦るな
今から説明してやる
We're going to drink from the same pot.
（時田）今回は
同じかめの酒を飲もうと思う
Especially since it’s a special trip.
（寿）せっかくの合宿だからな
You mean like eating from the same bowl?
（伊織）“同じ釜の飯”みたいな
もんですね
-By the way...
-It's hard to find a drink that everyone likes.
ところがだ
全員の好みが一致する酒ってのは
意外と難しい
That's true.
そりゃ そうですね
It would be sad if not everyone has a good time.
（時田）だが ここで みんなの
感想が異なるのは寂しいだろう
I guess you're right.
それは そうかもしれませんね
We want to make good drinking memories.
合宿の 思い出の酒ですし
-So we came up with an idea.
-To be fair...
（寿）だから 俺たちは考えたんだ
（寿･時田）
ならば 公平になるよう―
we're going to drink something everyone hates!
全員がキチい酒に
したらいいと！
That's what you're doing to be fair?
（伊織･耕平）公平の取り方
おかしくないですか!?
We're going to spin this pot,
（時田）で 今から
このかめを回して―
and have you pour in your favorite drink.
好きな酒を
注いでもらうわけだが
When you do, say a few words. Whatever you want.
そのとき なんでもいいから
ひと言 口上を述べてくれ
A few words?
口上？
In Otori, you're supposed to say a few words.
オトーリは 何か
ひと言 述べてやるものらしい
Like, "This is for the beautiful island and the ocean!"
“島と海の美しさにささげます”
とかな
I see.
なるほど
We're going to say a few serious things first.
まずは俺たちが 少し
真面目に話をさせてもらおう
We all come from different places,
出身地がバラバラの俺たちが
but we have gathered together
in the same time and place.
こうして 同じ時に
同じ場所に集い
I'm happy we could ride on the same boat,
and drink from the same pot.
同じ船に乗り 同じかめの酒を
飲めることをうれしく思う
Everyone here is a comrade and a friend.
この場にいる全員が
同好の士であり 仲間だ
Even if life leads us down separate paths,
いずれ それぞれの道は
分かれようとも
the time we spent together will never disappear.
共に過ごした時間は
なくならない
As a memory of your youth!
どうか 皆の人生における
青春の思い出として
Don't ever forget today!
今日という日を
忘れないでほしい！
SPIRYTUS (96%)
（部員たち）うおおお！
Yeah!
-Idiots!
-What do you mean, "memories of youth"?
（伊織）アホか！
（耕平）何が青春の思い出だ！
（伊織）思い出以前に
記憶すら残す気ないだろ！
You won't remember anything after drinking so much!
I'll never forget the time I spent with you guys!
俺 お前らと過ごした日々を
絶対 忘れねえからな！
SPIRYTUS (96%)
-Why are you pouring that in?
-You don't really plan on remembering this, do you?
本当に
覚えておく気があるのか!?
-I-- Azuma...
-Yeah?
ほれ 東
おう
ん…
-What's wrong, Azuma?
-I...
（横手）どうした 東
いや 俺 化学の勉強ばっか
やってきたから―
spent all my time studying chemistry.
I don't know what to say at times like these.
こういうとき
気の利いたことができなくてさ
So at least...
だから せめて
俺のできることで…
I'm going to do whatever I can!
ETHANOL (FOR SANITATION)
（耕平･伊織）入れるな～！
Don't put that in!
We were just joking.
ハハハ 冗談だ
If we put this in, the alcohol percentage would go down.
こんなもん 混ぜたら
度数 下がっちまうぜ
ALCOHOL CONCENTRATION 60%
It's stronger than disinfectant alcohol?
消毒用アルコールより
キツいだと!?
That's not supposed to be drunk!
（伊織）これ 絶対
飲み物じゃねえ！
If we do a toast with that,
there's no guarantee we'll survive!
（伊織）こんなもんで乾杯したら
命の保証はない
Now it's come down to this...
（耕平）かくなる上は…
（伊織）何食わぬ顔で
水でも入れて…
Let's put some water in and act like nothing happened.
（耕平）度数を安全圏まで下げる
Let's lower the alcohol percentage to a safe level.
Hey, you guys go too.
（東）ほら お前らも
-Okay!
-Sure!
（耕平）はい！
（伊織）分かりました
（伊織）あ…
My eyes!
目が！　目が！
（横手）グフッ！
だ 大丈夫ですか!?
Are you okay?
ああ 大丈夫だ
I'm okay.
Hey, hey! What are you doing?
（東）おいおい 何やってんだ
-Sorry.
-Don't worry about it.
すみません…
（横手）なに 気にするな
You’re not mad at me?
（耕平）怒らないんですか？
No one in PaB would get mad
over something as trivial as that.
このくらいでキレるようなガキは
ＰａＢにはいねえよ
Yokote...
先輩…
Then I'll put mine in too.
じゃ 俺のも入れますね
（東）んっ！
おう コラ 伊織！
-Hey, Iori!
-Knock it off!
ふざけたまね
してんじゃねえぞ
Elbowing you is okay, but not this?
ひじ打ちはＯＫなのに？
You're getting mad about the wrong thing!
キレるポイント おかしいだろ
（伊織）そ それならせめて
-Then at least...
-How about this?
これでなんとか
AWAMORI (60%)
（東）うーむ
（横手）まあ ギリギリ認めよう
Well, I guess I can accept it.
-Wait, you guys.
-You have to say a few words first.
待て待て お前ら
その前に 何かひと言だろう
（耕平）ビクッ！
（伊織）ああ そういえば…
Oh, you're right.
What's wrong, Kohei?
（伊織）どうした？　耕平
I can't come up with anything.
口上が思いつかん
What? You're not good at things like this?
なんだ こういうの苦手なのか
What should I do?
（耕平）どうしたらいいんだ…
（伊織）うーん… 改めて
自己紹介でもしたらどうだ？
Why don't you introduce yourself?
Okay. Then...
なるほど！　じゃあ―
I can say my name, my hobby, and my favorite quote.
名前と趣味と
座右の銘あたりでも言っておくか
That's good enough.
（伊織）それで十分だろ
All right, freshmen.
んじゃ １年ども
Let's have a few words.
口上を述べてくれ
はい
-Okay.
-Name, hobby, favorite quote...
名前 趣味 座右の銘
名前 趣味 座右の銘…
Name, hobby, favorite quote...
（せきばらい）
え～
Thanks to this club, I realized how great--
俺は このサークルのおかげで
ずっと嫌いだった…
-Kohei Imamura!
--is, even though I used to hate it.
今村(いまむら)耕平！
（伊織）の魅力に気付きました
-Even though I got dragged into--
-Anime and games!
最初は流されて始めた…
（耕平）アニメとゲーム！
も 今では
いいものだと思っています
--at first, I think it's really great now.
I'll work hard so that someday,
I'll be able to say--
これからは 一層 努力して
自分から…
（女声）
耕平おにいちゃん 結婚して
-Kohei, marry me!
--I'm going to do my best!
と言えるよう 頑張りたいと…
Knock it off!
ざけんな コラァ！
（耕平）ごふっ！
-What are you doing?
-That's what I was about to say!
てめえ 何しやがる！
それは こっちのセリフだ！
That was a good speech.
なかなか いいスピーチだったな
They talked about how they grew closer to each other.
まさか ２人の距離が縮んでいく
経緯を語るとは
（梓･奈々華）うんうん
（愛菜･千紗）うわあ…
All right. Everyone has a drink, right?
（時田）さて 全員 酒はあるな？
-They didn't have to fill it this full.
-Look, Kitahara.
ここまで
たっぷり注がんでも…
見ろ 北原　正しいオトーリの
作法が載ってるぞ
This explains how to do Otori right.
What? That means...
なんだと!?
ってことは これを見せれば…
If we show them this...
We don't have to drink like this!
この飲み方から 解放される！
Hey. Look at this.
先輩 見てください
（寿･時田）ん？
About Miyakojima Otori.
（伊織）
宮古島特有 オトーリとは
The leader says a few words and takes a drink.
親になった人が
口上を述べて飲み
（耕平）その後
全員が順番に飲み
After that, everyone drinks when it's their turn.
Finally, the leader drinks again,
（伊織）最後に 親が再び飲み
and says a few words again
before switching with the next leader.
（耕平）親が 後口上を述べて
次の親に交代
This repeats for each person.
（伊織）これを 人数分繰り返す
-I see.
-That means...
なるほど
（寿）ということは…
We have to do at least twelve toasts!
最低 12回は
乾杯する必要があるなあ
We don't have enough alcohol for that.
そうなると 酒が足らんな
Let's put all of this in.
この辺のも 全部入れるか
I didn't expect that to happen!
-We're used to strong drinks!
-You're right.
まあいい
強い酒は飲み慣れている！
確かに！
それより今 大事なのは…
The important thing right now is...
the strength of mind to avoid drowning in alcohol!
（伊織）酒を飲んでも飲まれない
という 強い精神力！
（伊織･耕平）ウエ～イ！
（東）いいぞ！　お前ら！
（横手）さすが 俺たちの後輩だ！
-Great, guys!
-That's it!
We've seen this many times already.
あっという間に
見慣れた光景に…
（千紗）ハァ…
（奈々華）みんな 楽しそうねえ
-They look like they're having fun.
-This is so relaxing.
落ち着くねえ
（時田）ん？
（寿）どうした？
What's wrong?
-We're out of booze.
-Already?
酒が切れた
（伊織）もうですか？
No wonder. You drank so much.
そりゃ あんな飲み方
してたらね…
Thanks for going out to buy some.
（時田）じゃあ 買い出し 頼むぞ
Sure.
（愛菜）ハァ… 分かりました
Sorry. Everyone else is drunk.
すまんな ほかはみんな
酒 入っててな
It's too much to carry alone. Help me.
１人じゃ大変だから
手伝ってよ
（伊織）ん？　ああ そうだよな
Oh, you're right.
Hold on. What are you doing?
ちょっと待って
何 考えてるの？
Oh, sorry. I didn't notice.
ん？　おお 悪い悪い
つい うっかり
Aren't we going?
行かないのか？
I wasn't trying to tell you to put on your seatbelt!
シートベルトをしろって
意味じゃない！
My first trip to a tropical island...
（愛菜）初めて訪れた
南の島で過ごす夜
Night has arrived.
The sky high above and the wide sea set me free...
高い空と 広い海は
最高の開放感
Maybe that's why...
だからなのかな…
this idiot...
このバカが
裸で外に出ちゃったのは
went outside naked.
I can't believe this!
本当に信じられない！
I didn't notice. Don't be so mad.
つい うっかりだったんだ
そう 怒るなよ
What's wrong?
どうした？
こいつ この格好で
車から降りたんですよ！
He got out of the car dressed like that!
It was really warm.
あまりに暖かかったんで
ふむ 道理だな
No wonder.
Resorts feel so liberating.
リゾート地ならではの
開放感ってやつか
It happens a lot.
よくあることだ
Why are you all agreeing with Iori?
どうして全員
伊織に賛同するの!?
-But, Cakey, think about it.
-What?
（伊織）だが ケバ子
よく考えてくれ
何よ！
A tropical island, a starry sky,
going for a drive with a guy...
（伊織）南の島 満天の星
男と２人でドライブ
These are the memories of youth you wanted, right?
これこそ お前が言う
青春じゃないか！
Maybe if the guy wasn't a half-naked pervert.
（愛菜）相手が
半裸の変態じゃなければね
I see. Sorry.
そうか すまん
（愛菜）分かってもらえた？
-Do you understand now?
-But even for me...
だが いくら俺でも
全裸というのは…
-Going fully naked is hard.
-I wasn't trying to say you didn't strip enough!
脱ぎ方が足りないって
意味じゃないから！
You don't have to take your clothes off
when you drink, do you?
そもそも 飲むときも
脱ぐ必要ないでしょ！
Stop looking at me like you don't know
what I'm talking about!
何言ってるのか分からないって
顔をしなーい！
Hey, hey. Have a drink and relax.
（梓）まあまあ これでも飲んで
落ち着きなよ
Come on.
（愛菜）まったく…
（梓）あっ…
That's my...
そっちは 私の…
（グラスが落ちる音）
（愛菜）あっ…
（愛菜）はにゃ…
（梓）ありゃ
What was in that?
（伊織）
それ 何が入ってたんです？
The leftovers from Otori.
（時田）
さっきのオトーリの残りだな
I diluted it though.
（梓）一応 ２倍に
薄めたんだけどねえ
But it's still over 30 percent.
（耕平）それでも
30度以上はあるんですが…
But this isn't bad either.
でも これはこれで
It's quiet now.
静かになって いいかもな
（愛菜）あ…
-What?
-You woke up?
なんだ
（耕平）起きたのか
はあ…
Hey, Iori.
（愛菜）ねえ 伊織
（伊織）ん？　どうした
-What's wrong?
-Iori, you're...
（愛菜）伊織ってさ 鈍いよね
-really dull, aren't you?
-What do you mean?
なんだ いきなり
俺のどこが鈍いんだよ
What's dull about me?
You are dull!
（愛菜）鈍いよ！
だって 私のアピールに―
You didn't notice
what I was trying to tell you.
全然 気付いてくれないんだもん
（耕平）ブーッ！
（伊織）はあ？
What are you talking about?
一体 なんの話だ
I thought about it.
（愛菜）私 思ったの
You're dull, so you wouldn't get it even if I told you.
伊織は鈍いから
言っても伝わらない
I have to show you through my actions.
行動で示すしかないって
（伊織）ん…
Cakey, are we about to get to the true end?
ケバ子 まさか
その先は トゥルーエンド…
I can't take it anymore!
If you don't get it no matter what I say,
私 もう我慢できない！
いくら言っても
伝わらないなら―
then I'll just--
いっそ…
（伊織）うぐっ
I'll watch. Take it off.
じっくり見とっちゃるけん
脱ぎんしゃい
Oh, so that's what you meant.
（耕平）
ああ 気持ちって そっちか…
いや そう言われると なんか…
-Now that you say that--
-Oh, I see. I see.
（愛菜）ほうほう そうかそうか
Or else...
なら うちが… 脱がしちゃる！
I'll take it off for you!
ま… 待て！　落ち着け！
Wait! Calm down!
You're next, Kohei!
次は耕平 あんたばい！
（耕平）なに!?
What?
（カラスの鳴き声）
That was bad.
（伊織）ヤバかったな
It was just one drink. She totally changed.
（耕平）たった１杯で
あそこまでひょう変するとは…
If you hadn't gotten out of the car naked--
そもそも お前が
裸で車から降りなければ！
Then you should have gone shopping!
（伊織）なら お前が
買い出しに行けばよかっただろ！
（愛菜）グルル… そっちか～！
There you are!
（伊織･耕平）ヤベえ！
Oh, no!
（伊織）フゥ…
（耕平）やれやれ
Oh, dear...
I can't get TV reception.
おのれ…
テレビの電波が入らん
-You're recording it anyway, right?
-You bastard.
どうせ 録画してあんだろ？
貴様 リアルタイムの
重要性を知らんのか
Don't you know it's important to see it live?
-No.
-But...
知らん
（耕平）
しかし 改めて考えるとアレだ
Now that I think about it...
（伊織）ん？
I never imagined I'd join a club like this.
（耕平）まさか この俺が
こんなサークルに入るとはな
I think it suits you well.
お前には
よく似合ってると思うがな
Are you trying to start a fight?
ケンカ売ってるのか コラ
I joined because you tricked me!
そもそも 俺は
お前にだまされて入ったんだ！
むっ… “だました”は
人聞きが悪いな
I tricked you? Don't say that.
まさか 違うとでも言う気か？
Are you trying to say it's not true?
-No.
-Hurry up and go.
（伊織）違う
（耕平）いけしゃあしゃあと…
Your wish came true, right?
（伊織）だって お前の希望は
かなったじゃないか
（耕平）どこが!?
（伊織）ほら 言ってただろ
-What do you mean?
-You said it, right?
You said you thought the life of your dreams
was waiting for you at college.
“大学に来たら
夢のような生活が―”
“待ってると思ってた”って
（耕平）あ…
This is like a dream, right?
この生活も ある意味
夢みたいなもんだろ？
（耕平）あ…
フッ… ああ そうだな
Yeah. You're right.
-More like a nightmare than a dream.
-That's right.
夢と言っても 悪夢だがな
（伊織）違いない
What? You don't know when to give up!
（愛菜）ええい 往生際の悪か！
（伊織･耕平）イヤー！
（千紗）ウフッ
（梓）ん？
Chii-chan, where did you get those?
ちーちゃん
どうしたの？　それ
At the convenience store.
コンビニでプリントして…
Wow, nice shot.
へえ きれいに撮れてるわね
The image quality is good, but...
画質はきれいなんだけど…
What a huge gap.
ひどいギャップが…
（梓）ウフッ
I like both of them.
（奈々華）私は両方とも好きよ
That's exactly how we are.
（梓）これこそ
ウチって感じだよね
♪～
～♪
What are they doing?
何やってんだか